{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350090020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350090020"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 6f962eeb-1146-404d-b626-1cba941d7fb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350096245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350096244"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 6f962eeb-1146-404d-b626-1cba941d7fb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350103911","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350103911"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 6f962eeb-1146-404d-b626-1cba941d7fb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350131084","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350131084"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" b0f700c8-8b8c-4cfd-a5de-8d5b27aab09d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350178034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350178033"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" b0f700c8-8b8c-4cfd-a5de-8d5b27aab09d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350178128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350178128"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" b0f700c8-8b8c-4cfd-a5de-8d5b27aab09d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAGA"," userResponse":" KUSAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350190090","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350190090"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-Z-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350195920","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350195920"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-Z-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350198948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350198948"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-B-Y"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350204530","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350204530"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-B-Y"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350209169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350209169"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_E-T-Y"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350214584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350214584"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-A-R"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350218796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350218796"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_S-P-M"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350224142","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350224142"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-U-S"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350228262","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350228261"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_B-A-L"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350232952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350232952"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_G-N-Y"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350239936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350239936"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_J-A-CH"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350247601","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350247601"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_J-A-CH"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350262388","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350262388"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_J-A-CH"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350266200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350266200"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_S-D-W"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350270727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350270727"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-K-F"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350275955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350275955"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_O-G-S"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350279732","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350279732"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_M-CH-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350283928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350283928"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_G-N-CH"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350287859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350287859"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_J-K-Y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350296088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350296088"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_I-W-O"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350300352","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350300352"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-O-T"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350304181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350304181"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_B-R-T"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350308002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350308002"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-Y-R"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350311602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350311602"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_N-D-I"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350315421","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350315421"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-D-Z"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350318876","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350318876"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-T-K"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350323036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350323036"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_M-I-CH"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350327939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350327939"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_P-F-L"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350333703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350333702"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_F_P-F-L"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350340243","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350340243"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_F_P-F-L"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350347090","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350347090"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" c2c031d4-c5a3-4aae-9a7a-9326ebb9dd9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_F_P-F-L"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350356983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350356982"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350360207","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350360207"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350361790","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350361790"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350364518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350364517"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350366111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350366110"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350368928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350368928"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350370527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350370526"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350378247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350378246"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350379892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350379890"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350384705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350384704"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350386284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350386284"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350392507","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350392507"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350394145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350394144"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350400501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350400500"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350402118","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350402118"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANASOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350407636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350407635"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANASOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350409204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350409204"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350412496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350412496"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350414133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350414133"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ASALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350417775","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350417775"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ASALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350419343","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350419342"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350421756","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350421756"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350423766","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350423765"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350423850","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350423850"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 2338c9b3-d1ba-4db3-b5c0-de20b334419c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350437386","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350437386"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 285cc8ca-eedf-4719-9930-25e69add3a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350446151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350446151"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 285cc8ca-eedf-4719-9930-25e69add3a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350447747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350447747"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 285cc8ca-eedf-4719-9930-25e69add3a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350451306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350451306"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 285cc8ca-eedf-4719-9930-25e69add3a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350452265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350452264"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 285cc8ca-eedf-4719-9930-25e69add3a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" START_ANDAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350452884","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350452882"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 285cc8ca-eedf-4719-9930-25e69add3a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350461945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350461944"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 285cc8ca-eedf-4719-9930-25e69add3a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350462064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350462064"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 285cc8ca-eedf-4719-9930-25e69add3a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350471861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350471859"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 285cc8ca-eedf-4719-9930-25e69add3a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350480677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350480677"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 285cc8ca-eedf-4719-9930-25e69add3a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350488300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350488300"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 285cc8ca-eedf-4719-9930-25e69add3a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350500762","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350500762"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4537f226-ff1f-4e1b-84c9-c7c0377a8b91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_3-0-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350511988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350511987"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4537f226-ff1f-4e1b-84c9-c7c0377a8b91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-5-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350519520","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350519520"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4537f226-ff1f-4e1b-84c9-c7c0377a8b91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350528318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350528318"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4537f226-ff1f-4e1b-84c9-c7c0377a8b91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-9-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350537743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350537742"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4537f226-ff1f-4e1b-84c9-c7c0377a8b91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-4-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350545642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350545642"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4537f226-ff1f-4e1b-84c9-c7c0377a8b91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_0-3-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350552512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350552512"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4537f226-ff1f-4e1b-84c9-c7c0377a8b91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_2-6-1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350561572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350561572"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4537f226-ff1f-4e1b-84c9-c7c0377a8b91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-4-2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350568835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350568834"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4537f226-ff1f-4e1b-84c9-c7c0377a8b91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_5-7-8"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350574631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350574631"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4537f226-ff1f-4e1b-84c9-c7c0377a8b91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-9-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350581184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350581184"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4537f226-ff1f-4e1b-84c9-c7c0377a8b91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-9-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415187347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415187347"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 00e5addb-ebd1-457b-98b9-3ee03d61a709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-B-CH"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415191159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415191158"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 00e5addb-ebd1-457b-98b9-3ee03d61a709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-B-CH"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415220908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415220908"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 6c655f6c-affd-4ade-89b9-da4e44efbe12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415245024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415245024"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 6c655f6c-affd-4ade-89b9-da4e44efbe12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415247386","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415247385"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 6c655f6c-affd-4ade-89b9-da4e44efbe12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415250495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415250495"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 6c655f6c-affd-4ade-89b9-da4e44efbe12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415275637","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415275637"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 6c655f6c-affd-4ade-89b9-da4e44efbe12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415277854","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415277854"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 6c655f6c-affd-4ade-89b9-da4e44efbe12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415309270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415309269"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 6c655f6c-affd-4ade-89b9-da4e44efbe12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415309376","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415309376"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 6c655f6c-affd-4ade-89b9-da4e44efbe12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415315522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415315521"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 6c655f6c-affd-4ade-89b9-da4e44efbe12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415321786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415321785"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 6c655f6c-affd-4ade-89b9-da4e44efbe12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415331287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415331287"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 409b402a-7fa2-4384-9482-d69a83c725e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_U-A-N"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415336312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415336312"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 409b402a-7fa2-4384-9482-d69a83c725e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_U-A-N"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415340464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415340464"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 409b402a-7fa2-4384-9482-d69a83c725e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_B-K-A"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415344052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415344051"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 409b402a-7fa2-4384-9482-d69a83c725e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-H-E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415347204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415347204"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 409b402a-7fa2-4384-9482-d69a83c725e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_Y-M-A"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415352565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415352565"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 409b402a-7fa2-4384-9482-d69a83c725e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_Y-M-A"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415356349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415356349"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 409b402a-7fa2-4384-9482-d69a83c725e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-B-CH"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415359802","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415359802"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 409b402a-7fa2-4384-9482-d69a83c725e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_F-A-U"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415363312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415363312"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 409b402a-7fa2-4384-9482-d69a83c725e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_R-A-F"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415368655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415368654"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 409b402a-7fa2-4384-9482-d69a83c725e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_R-A-F"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415371724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415371724"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 409b402a-7fa2-4384-9482-d69a83c725e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-M-B"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415377017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415377016"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 409b402a-7fa2-4384-9482-d69a83c725e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-M-B"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415380705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415380705"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 409b402a-7fa2-4384-9482-d69a83c725e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-N-T"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415384542","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415384542"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 409b402a-7fa2-4384-9482-d69a83c725e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_J-A-H"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415390297","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415390297"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 409b402a-7fa2-4384-9482-d69a83c725e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_A_J-A-H"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415456101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415456100"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" f1afa836-e7d3-47bb-b596-e5e3b4ac979c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vile_kitu-vile-nguvu-maji"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" vile"," userResponse":" vile"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415482327","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415482326"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" f1afa836-e7d3-47bb-b596-e5e3b4ac979c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makali_mwangaza-makali-muhimu-hizi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" makali"," userResponse":" muhimu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415485013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415485013"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" f1afa836-e7d3-47bb-b596-e5e3b4ac979c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makali_mwangaza-makali-muhimu-hizi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" makali"," userResponse":" makali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415517765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415517764"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" f1afa836-e7d3-47bb-b596-e5e3b4ac979c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gani_nani-gani-hiki-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" gani"," userResponse":" gani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415536938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415536938"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" f1afa836-e7d3-47bb-b596-e5e3b4ac979c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makubwa_tayari-hebu-umri-makubwa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" makubwa"," userResponse":" makubwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415553950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415553949"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" f1afa836-e7d3-47bb-b596-e5e3b4ac979c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbele_mbele-nyuma-kuliko-si"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mbele"," userResponse":" mbele"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415568794","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415568792"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" f1afa836-e7d3-47bb-b596-e5e3b4ac979c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mbele_mbele-nyuma-kuliko-si"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415568953","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415568953"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" f1afa836-e7d3-47bb-b596-e5e3b4ac979c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANGAPI"," userResponse":" MANGAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415575435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415575434"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" f1afa836-e7d3-47bb-b596-e5e3b4ac979c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415580912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415580911"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" f1afa836-e7d3-47bb-b596-e5e3b4ac979c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415587171","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415587170"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" f1afa836-e7d3-47bb-b596-e5e3b4ac979c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415616818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415616818"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 16f8d34f-9ec9-4383-bd06-5061e0242c65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakati_kwenda-baada-katika-wakati"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" wakati"," userResponse":" wakati"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415642206","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415642206"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 16f8d34f-9ec9-4383-bd06-5061e0242c65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakati_wakati-karibu-katika-mimi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" wakati"," userResponse":" wakati"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415692095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415692093"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 16f8d34f-9ec9-4383-bd06-5061e0242c65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" wakati_wakati-karibu-katika-mimi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415692210","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415692209"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 16f8d34f-9ec9-4383-bd06-5061e0242c65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415706571","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415706571"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 16f8d34f-9ec9-4383-bd06-5061e0242c65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415711810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415711810"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 16f8d34f-9ec9-4383-bd06-5061e0242c65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415718368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415718368"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 16f8d34f-9ec9-4383-bd06-5061e0242c65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415724051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415724050"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 16f8d34f-9ec9-4383-bd06-5061e0242c65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415730877","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415730877"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 16f8d34f-9ec9-4383-bd06-5061e0242c65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415738217","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415738217"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 16f8d34f-9ec9-4383-bd06-5061e0242c65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415743943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415743942"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 16f8d34f-9ec9-4383-bd06-5061e0242c65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415752395","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415752395"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 16f8d34f-9ec9-4383-bd06-5061e0242c65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415762412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415762412"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415763266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415763266"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415764289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415764289"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415764534","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415764533"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415765087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415765087"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415765650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415765650"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415766185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415766185"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415770013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415770013"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAFUTA"," userResponse":" ALITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415770759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415770759"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415771152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415771152"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415771967","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415771967"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415773041","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415773041"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415773836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415773836"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415777125","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415777125"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415778671","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415778671"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHAMBULIA"," userResponse":" ANASHAMBULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415781684","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415781684"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415781948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415781948"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415782663","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415782663"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415783468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415783468"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415783923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415783923"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415784619","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415784619"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415785353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415785352"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415786548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415786548"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFURAHI"," userResponse":" ANAFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415789737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415789736"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415789832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415789832"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFURAHI"," userResponse":" ANAFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415796252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415796252"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 59e1122b-4261-4ebf-b13d-cbe3691a7c98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415807358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415807358"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415809504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415809504"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415811610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415811610"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415814787","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415814787"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415817007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415817007"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415819214","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415819214"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415822022","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415822021"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415824200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415824199"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415826373","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415826373"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415829556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415829556"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415831656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415831656"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415833792","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415833791"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415836801","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415836801"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415839039","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415839039"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415841278","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415841277"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415844655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415844655"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415847049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415847049"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415849455","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415849454"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415852515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415852515"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415854673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415854673"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415856842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415856841"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415859982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415859982"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415862164","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415862163"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415864367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415864367"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415867550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415867550"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415869979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415869979"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415872409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415872409"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415875555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415875555"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415877789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415877789"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415880012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415880012"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415884524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415884524"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415886814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415886814"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415889037","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415889037"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415892038","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415892038"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415894516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415894516"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415897592","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415897592"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415900828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415900828"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415903197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415903197"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415905580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415905580"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415908571","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415908571"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415910837","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415910837"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415913094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415913094"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415916316","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415916316"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415918547","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415918547"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415920814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415920813"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415924232","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415924232"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415926648","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415926648"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415929061","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415929061"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415931873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415931873"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415934057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415934057"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415936245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415936243"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415939655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415939654"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415941957","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415941957"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415944302","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415944302"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415947436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415947435"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415950699","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415950699"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415952928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415952928"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415955941","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415955941"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415958039","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415958039"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415960126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415960125"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415963288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415963288"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415965502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415965502"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415967730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415967730"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415970909","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415970908"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415973104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415973104"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415975285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415975285"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415978519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415978519"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415980817","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415980816"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415983112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415983112"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415986154","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415986154"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415988453","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415988453"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415990749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415990749"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415999829","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415999829"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548415999910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548415999909"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 4e35cfd4-06ed-40f7-9e9a-e588d4d60061"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416010027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416010027"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416012140","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416012140"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416014268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416014268"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416017443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416017443"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416019672","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416019672"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416021906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416021906"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416024736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416024735"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416026903","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416026903"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416029067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416029067"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416032238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416032238"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416034336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416034336"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416036461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416036461"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416039965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416039965"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416042147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416042147"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416044339","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416044338"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416047306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416047306"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416049638","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416049638"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416051963","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416051963"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416054976","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416054975"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416057068","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416057068"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416059181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416059181"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416062317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416062317"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416066245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416066244"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416068403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416068403"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416071599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416071599"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416074044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416074044"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416076467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416076467"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416079566","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416079566"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416081851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416081851"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416084146","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416084146"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416087072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416087072"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416089296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416089296"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416091529","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416091529"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416094439","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416094438"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416096742","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416096742"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416099063","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416099063"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416102241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416102241"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416104572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416104571"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416106902","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416106902"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416109811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416109811"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416112057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416112057"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416114302","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416114302"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416117487","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416117487"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416119748","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416119748"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416121980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416121980"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416125372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416125371"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416127796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416127796"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416130195","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416130195"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416131562","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416131561"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416131736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416131736"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 08b44381-12f2-4046-98b4-e4f8b541b44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416141665","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416141665"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416143786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416143786"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416145879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416145879"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416151162","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416151162"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416153473","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416153472"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416155765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416155765"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416158631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416158630"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416160816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416160816"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416163073","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416163072"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416166247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416166247"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416168348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416168348"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416170430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416170430"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416173365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416173365"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416175574","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416175574"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416177764","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416177764"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416180779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416180779"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416183111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416183111"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416185559","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416185558"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416188607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416188607"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416190798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416190798"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416192947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416192947"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416196048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416196048"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416198223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416198223"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416200423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416200423"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416203626","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416203625"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416206018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416206018"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416208401","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416208401"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416211466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416211465"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416220013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416220013"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416222302","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416222301"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416225248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416225248"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416225474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416225474"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416225575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416225575"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548416244658","data":{"timestamp":" 1548416244658"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_201441"," gameId":" 31d9ab97-0518-4852-93c1-9ede03c807f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}